<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><title>Salma Ghareeb</title><link>https://salmaghareeb.me/</link><description>Recent blog posts on Salma Ghareeb</description><generator>Hugo (https://gohugo.io)</generator><language>en-us</language><managingEditor>salmaghareeb@gmail.com (Salma Ghareeb)</managingEditor><webMaster>salmaghareeb@gmail.com (Salma Ghareeb)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 22:37:45 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://salmaghareeb.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>1-1 Feedback as a professional</title><link>https://salmaghareeb.me/feedback/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 22:37:45 +0800</pubDate><author>salmaghareeb@gmail.com (Salma Ghareeb)</author><description>
I&amp;amp;rsquo;ve been thinking about feedback and how it can be a powerful tool for growth and improvement. I&amp;amp;rsquo;ve realized that feedback is not just about pointing out mistakes or shortcomings, but also about sharing insights and perspectives that can help others learn and develop. I&amp;amp;rsquo;ve also learned that feedback is not just about giving feedback, but also about receiving feedback and being open to it.
# When does feedback come hand in hand? Situations Team member, you don’t get along with? Hierarchy changes that are affecting you? Not able to voice your opinion because some colleagues cut you off? # What’s the intent of giving feedback? Make things better, for you and the team. Defining and communicating your boundaries and working style.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://salmaghareeb.me/feedback/</guid></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://salmaghareeb.me/posts/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate><author>salmaghareeb@gmail.com (Salma Ghareeb)</author><description>
Hi, I’m Salma — a software engineer based in Berlin with a focus on building reliable systems and clear communication. I’ve spent the last few years working mostly in backend development with Go.
This site is a mix of things I’m learning, experimenting with, or reflecting on — from tech topics and architecture ideas to notes on collaboration and personal growth. I’m especially interested in simplifying complex problems, writing code that’s easy to reason about, and navigating the human side of engineering.</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://salmaghareeb.me/posts/about/</guid></item></channel></rss>